Jorge Kenneth C. Nuezca

Dubai Marina, Dubai, United Arab Emirates Cell: (+971) 525284721 nuezcajorge@gmail.com

SUMMARY

High-performing Web Developer and Content Specialist/Producer, who easily adapts to constantly changing web services and programming applications. More than three years of experience influencing positive organizational outcomes by developing websites using various technologies such as HTML, CSS (SASS, SCSS), PHP, JQuery, and JavaScript including certain frameworks. Capable of working on a team and several projects at once while meeting deadlines under pressure, and self-assured in capacity to work with cross-functional teams to solve difficult and high-stakes issues. Dedicated to continuous improvement and to team success.

SKILLS

Industry Knowledge: Web Content Optimization, SEO, Plugin Development, Theme Development,

Cross-browser Compatibility, cPanel, Leaflet

Multimedia Software: Photoshop, Premier, Fireworks, Adobe XD, Figma

Web Tools & Technologies: HTML, CSS (SASS, SCSS), Bootstrap, JavaScript, JQuery, Vue.js, PHP,

WordPress, WooCommerce

Database Systems: MySQL, SQL, MongoDB

Version Control: Git, Gitlab

Other Software: Notepad++, Sublime Text, Visual Studio Code

Tools: XAMPP, WAMP, WinSCP

EXPERIENCE

GLOBAL APPCASTING - Content Producer & Web Developer

July 2019 – Present

Thailand (Remote)

- Handled work for the Advertising team and did Quality Assurance of tasks.
- Provided asset creation on multiple projects.
- Responsible for site maintenance, research and production for the contents of client magazines
- Managed different ad boards for Sports & Health, Football, Fashion, Design, Beauty & Luxury.
- Gathered information and entered data into the production system.
- Ensured that tasks assigned (moderate and critical) are delivered with quality and on time.
- Supported the solution to additional features and capabilities based on user requirements.
- Attended meeting and contributed to project and initiated brainstorming.
- Contributed to the product platform's architecture.
- Prepared and submitted reports requested by supervisor or team lead.
- Provided recommendations to improve processes and quality of work.
- Collaborated with team members to design and develop robust, scalable software solutions.

Baguio City, Philippines

- Translated wireframes into web templates and graphics for use in a content management system.
- Resolved client issues by establishing workarounds and solutions by debugging and creating defect fixes.
- Updated, modified, expanded existing websites, and drafted technical documents.
- WordPress customizations using Advanced Custom Fields (ACF).
- Optimizing website for maximum speed and scalability.
- Wrote well-designed, testable, efficient code by using best software development practices.
- Integrated data from various back-end services and databases.
- Took proactively care of further development and optimization of the business process within the system.
- Performed project tasks according to project plans and managed changes to the web system.
- Ensured web projects are compatible and responsive across multiple browsers and devices.

Outhouse On-the-Job Training

Short term (2017)

Philippine Statistics Authority – CAR

Statistical Operations and Coordination Division (SOCD) 320 hours

- Managed the database for the RSET
- Created a site using PHP and SQL to create, read, update, delete statistical data about the Regional Social and Economic Trend for Benguet Region.

Inhouse On-the-Job Training

1st Semester (2015 – 2016)

 SCIS, Deans Office, Silang Building Saint Louis University 200 hours

PROJECTS

Portfolio Website	https://portfolio-kenneth.vercel.app/		
Brookline Dental Specialists	https://www.brookline-dental.com/		
Design Drafting Services	https://designdraftingservicesgroup.com		

Pioneer Realty https://pioneerrealty.com/
Other Projects Available upon request

EDUCATION & TRAININGS

PYTHON BASICS FOR DATA SCIENCE

2022

IBM PY0101EN - edX Online Learning

VUE - THE COMPLETE GUIDE

2022

Udemy Online Course

WEB DEVELOPMENT BOOTCAMP

2022

Udemy Online Course

COLUMN	787 8		TENTA TEN	TOTAL A TRITATO
COMSERV	/ Hi — H	"K()	NTHIND	TRAINING

2021

TERTIARY 2012 - 2017

Saint Louis University

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

Bonifacio Street, Baguio City, Benguet 2600, Philippines

SECONDARY 2008 - 2012

Home Oriented Prime Education (H.O.P.E) Christian Academy Inc.

La Trinidad, Benguet 2601, Philippines

REFERENCES:

Available upon request